lendacademy.com 2018-12-29

# Lend Academy Privacy Policy - Lend Academy

_As of May 25, 2018_

Welcome to Lend Academy! We are committed to providing our customers, visitors, partners and employees with clarity about how we collect, use and protect personal data. 

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the collection, use and disclosure of information collected online by our website at www.LendAcademy.com (including any subpages or mobile versions thereof) or any other website where this policy is posted (each, a “Site” and collectively the “Sites”). 

The Policy forms an agreement between you, or if you are using these Sites on behalf of an entity, that entity and Lend Academy. In this document, “Lend Academy,” “we,” “us” and “our” refer to Lend Academy (operated by Renton Media, LLC) and “you” and “user” refers to the parties – known as “data subjects” in certain privacy regulations – to which this privacy policy (“Policy”) applies. 

Lend Academy uses data primarily to help readers and subscribers of our content to make the most of their experience; and to communicate news about upcoming events for our affiliated company, LendIt Conference, LLC, that individuals and companies may be interested in attending. A detailed list of data uses is further below.

Through your continued use of our Sites or by willingly providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to the practices described in this Policy. 

## Communications & Data Collection Preference Settings

You may visit the following links to customize your preferences for receiving email communications, for aspects of data collection, and for use of cookies during visits to our Sites:

  * Lend Academy Communications Preferences for email communications and data collection. Communication preferences can be managed at the bottom of bi-weekly newsletters by clicking “Change Subscriber Options” or the “Unsubscribe” links within. 
  * Lend Academy Cookie Preferences __

Cookie Settings  

## Contact

Lend Academy   
Ms. Jamie Zynger, Director of Finance & Accounting  
66 S. Logan St, Suite 208  
Denver, CO 80209  

## What Information do we collect and how do we use it?

For the purposes of this Policy, “Personal Information” means any information that can be used to help identify you as an individual, including your: name; address; online/social media accounts; employment information, email and telephone number; and any persistent identifier that can be used to recognize you over time and your activity across different services. 

We also may compile “Other Relevant Information,” which doesn’t directly identify a user but may further characterize your interest and behavior. An example of this is your stated interest in Lend Academy content and activities focused on certain industry themes. Together, we refer to Personal Information and Other Relevant Information as “Personally Relevant Information.”

## _When you download content or register for an activity on our Site_

To stay abreast of industry trends or receive detailed materials about our programs, you may choose to take steps such as downloading an e-book or agenda, or register for a webinar.  Personally Relevant Information may be collected at that time, in order to fulfill the request. 

## _When you sign up to receive updates about Lend Academy_

When you proactively sign up for updates on Lend Academy, we will add you to our email list. This list provides news, updates on our conferences and other events, or other information you may find useful. Lend Academy, our sponsors, or partners will only use your Personal Information collected through this email sign-up in order to send you these communications.  You have the option to customize the types of information you receive, via our bi-weekly newsletters noted above.

## _When you read Lend Academy’s blog_

You may choose to opt-in to email communications from Lend Academy. This involves providing an email address, name and company information. This information will not be shared with third parties. You can later opt-out, if desired, by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any Lend Academy email. You may alternatively read Lend Academy without opting into emails.

## _When you contact us through the Site_

We request your name and email address if you contact us through our online contact form. We will use Personal Information collected through the contact form only as needed to respond to your inquiry. 

## _Third party sites and services_

Certain services on our site may be provided or powered by third parties. You may also visit other third party sites through links on our Site. While these parties may provide information to us, these third parties are not bound by this Policy and may have privacy policies of their own governing the use and disclosure of your Personal Information. Please read any policies of third parties before you choose to provide Personal Information to them.

## _Cookies and online tracking_

Our Site uses cookies and related tracking technologies to enhance the features, performance and personalization of the Site experience. While most of the cookies respect your anonymity during browsing online, some may follow your activity on the site in order to better personalize interactions. Our cookie management policy, and an option for you to determine preferences for cookie use during your visit to our Sites, can be found at [www.LendAcademy.com/cookies](https://www.lendacademy.com/cookies). 

## With whom may we share your Personal Information?

We respect the privacy of our readers and do not sell or provide access to your Personal Information.

We typically do not share your Personal Information with unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to complete a transaction or request. We reserve the right to share your Personal Information with our current or future affiliates, subsidiaries, parents, and partners who agree to abide by this policy.

Your Personal Information will be used with service providers who perform business functions on our behalf, or in the other circumstances noted below. For example, we may share certain Personal Information we collect with third parties such as providers of data hosting, accounting, processing services, CRM providers, or other providers of essential/internal business functions.

In limited circumstances, we may share Personal Information we possess as part of a sale or transfer of our business, or substantially all of our assets. We may also share Personal Information if we need to protect the interests of Lend Academy, our customers, property, or the public, to the extent allowed by law. Similarly, we may share Personal Information with governmental authorities or otherwise in response to a legal request that we believe requires us to do so. We will share any such information to the extent we believe that request requires. Legal requests include, for example, search warrants, subpoenas, and other court orders. We may also receive legal requests or orders from jurisdictions outside the United States, in which case you consent for your Personal Information to be transferred to the applicable country.

## What choices do I have about the collection, use, and disclosure of my personal or other information?

It is possible for you to use our Site without providing any Personal Information, but you may not be able to access delivered content. 

## How can I access or update my Personal Information?

You may access or update any Personal Information we hold about you by sending a letter or email using the contact information listed at the beginning of this Policy. We will provide you a statement of all data collected about you. We will respond to reasonable requests for revision and will provide access to the extent required by law. 

For residents of California (as required by California law) the Personal Information Lend Academy has disclosed about you to third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year (if any) is available upon request by contacting us.

## How long do you retain my personal information and communication preferences?

We consider your communication preferences to be current until you change your preferences.

You can unsubscribe at any time from all email newsletters and related communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of every email. 

You may request that we delete all of your personally identifiable information at any time by writing Lend Academy using the contact information at the top of this policy or opting out of all communications within our bi-weekly newsletter. We will acknowledge receipt of the request, fulfill it within 30 days and send you confirmation when complete.

## Is my Personal Information protected? What happens if there is a data breach?

We use reasonable security measures to protect any Personal Information held by Lend Academy. We implement and regularly review various physical, procedural and technological safeguards that we believe will keep your Personal Information secure.

When becoming aware of a breach or suspected breach, we will notify the relevant supervisory authority within 72 hours. When the personal data breach is likely to result in a high risk to your rights and freedoms, we shall communicate the personal data breach to you without undue delay.

## International guests

If you are accessing this Site from outside of the United States, you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States, and the processing, use, and sharing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We comply with the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield and related frameworks for international data transfer. Regardless of where your information is collected or transferred, the information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## Minor Users and COPPA

Lend Academy complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). This site is neither directed at nor intended for minors under the age of 18. In the event that we have inadvertently collected Personal Information from a user under age 13, we will promptly delete it, in compliance with COPPA. Do not use this Site if you are under the age of 18.

## Additional Agreements

This Policy is incorporated into our Terms of Use [https://www.lendacademy.com/terms](https://www.lendacademy.com/terms/) and may include terms that are defined in that agreement. You may also be bound by sponsorship, registration, or exhibitor terms and conditions, (each an “Additional Agreement”). In the event of a conflict between this Policy and an Additional Agreement, the Additional Agreement will supersede. Further, you may arrive at a third-party site or service when using our Site or a certain feature, in which case this Policy does not apply. Please review the policies of any third party to learn how they may treat your Personal Information.

## Limitation of liability

By providing us with any Personal information you expressly and unconditionally release and hold harmless Lend Academy, its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, related companies and their respective shareholders, owners, members, directors, officers, employees and agents (collectively, the “Releasees”) from any and all liability for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected Personal Information. In addition, while we take reasonable steps to prevent third-party companies from making unauthorized use of your personal information, we cannot be held liable for any injuries, loss or damage of any kind arising from or in connection with the use and/or misuse of your collected Personal Information by those third parties.

We embed a Facebook widget to allow you to see number of likes/shares/recommends and “like/share/recommend” our webpages. This widget may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the widget, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the widget (such as “liking/sharing/recommending” our webpage), if you are logged in to Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update>

We use a Twitter Tweet widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Twitter’s servers for you to be able to tweet our webpages using your Twitter account. These requests make your IP address visible to Twitter, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: [https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update](https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update)

We use a GooglePlus widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Google’s servers for you to be able to share our webpages using your GooglePlus account. These requests make your IP address visible to Google, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

We use a Linkedin Share widget at our website to allow you to share our webpages on Linkedin. These requests may track your IP address in accordance with their data privacy policy: <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy>

## Changes to this policy

This policy may change from time to time. We will post the most current version of this policy on our website with the effective date indicated. Your continued use of our Sites means you consent to the terms of any Policy revisions.
